<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>template on The views expressed</title><link>https://philoserf.com/terms/template/</link><description>Recent content in template on The views expressed</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://philoserf.com/terms/template/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Feature Template</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/feature-template/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/feature-template/</guid><description>Feature:NAME DESCRIPTION Background:NAME DESCRIPTION Given STEP_DESCRIPTION And STEP_DESCRIPTION Scenario Outline:NAME DESCRIPTION Given STEP_DESCRIPTION And STEP_DESCRIPTION &amp;#34;&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;&amp;#34; When STEP_DESCRIPTION But STEP_DESCRIPTION Then STEP_DESCRIPTION &amp;#34;&amp;lt;output&amp;gt;&amp;#34; And STEP_DESCRIPTION Example: |input|output||value|result||valve|result|</description></item><item><title>Desired outcome</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-desired-outcome/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-desired-outcome/</guid><description>Any result you want to achieve or experience you want to have.
This is a broad catch-all category, which is designed to give you permission to capture anything that you might want (as little or big as that might be).
Examples Go for a hot-air balloon ride. Do a yoga hand-stand. Take a fabulous vacation trout fishing. Spend a day doing nothing. Meet the perfect tennis coach. Create a wonderful family reunion for Mom and Dad’s 50th Anniversary.</description></item><item><title>Affirmation</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-affirmation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-affirmation/</guid><description>A written self-talk statement
Affirmations are statements about desired experiences or outcomes, written in the first-person present tense, with rich texture. Reading them should put you in the center of your own advertisements.
Examples I love the healthy way my body feels, toned and flexible, at its perfect weight. With positive cash flow and increasing financial reserves, I am experiencing an exhilarating sense of abundance and freedom. It is easy for me to express my affection for my family through my words and my touch.</description></item><item><title>Ideal scene</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-ideal-scene/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-ideal-scene/</guid><description>A detailed description of a desired future. Ideal scenes can take on many forms – mocked-up articles in the press describing how extraordinarily successful your enterprise has been, collages with pictures and headlines that express what your life may look and feel like if you could have it like you want it, etc. It can simply be descriptive paragraphs written in an affirmational style. Wonderful to create and re-read and re-imagine on some regular basis.</description></item><item><title>Intention</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-intention/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-intention/</guid><description>A resolve toward a direction, value, outcome or purpose.
An intention can be used to express an inclination toward something – a desire for a more on-going way of being or acting as well as specific goals or results.
Examples I am consistently improving the range of my vocabulary. I am trusting my own judgment, insights, and decisions. The company is providing a rich environment for people to expand their personal and professional capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Intuition</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-intuition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-intuition/</guid><description>Hunches about where things are going and optimal approaches to it.
Intuitive insights are seldom recognized when we have them. It’s useful to notice when an awareness may be present in you and feed it back to yourself at a future time. It can sensitize and enhance your perceptive abilities.
Examples By the end of the year, I sense I will have met someone whom I consider masterful at my new hobby.</description></item><item><title>One Pager</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/one-pager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/one-pager/</guid><description>The Problem How do we communicate clearly in a business or technological setting?
The Solution Write a One Pager.
To write a good One Pager:
Write it in one page. Put a date at the top, so people know if it’s fresh or stale. Write a clear, short title. Write a single sentence problem description in the form of a question. Write the smallest solution description possible, while being complete and clear.</description></item><item><title>20,000 feet</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-2/</guid><description>Areas of focus and responsibility Important spheres of work and life to be maintained at standards to “keep the engines running.”
This is a good checklist to review to ensure balance amidst all the roles you play and “hats” you wear. Review the whole list every so often, or pick one at a time and remind yourself at some interval: &amp;ldquo;How am I doing about XXXXX?&amp;rdquo;
Examples Work Staff development Planning Asset management Business development Quality control Personal Health/vitality Family Spiritual Career Recreation Household/administration Finances</description></item><item><title>30,000 feet</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-3/</guid><description>One- to two-year goals and objectives What do we want and need to accomplish, specifically, within the next 12 to 24 months, to make the vision happen?
Where is your job and personal life going? What will the role you’re in right now be looking like 12-24 months from now, based on your goals and on the directions of the changes at that level?
Examples Be debt free Company is 20% profitable Lose 10 pounds Sustain an exercise plan</description></item><item><title>40,000 feet</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-4/</guid><description>Three to five-year vision What it will look, sound, feel like with successful implementation. Long-term outcomes and ideal scenarios.
Visions represent larger outcomes that may take up to many years to create. Perhaps reviewed annually.
Examples Known as the leading innovator in our industry, internationally. Have written a best-selling novel. Shooting par golf. Being conversational in two more languages. Have established a not-for-profit foundation recognized for its contributions to the community.</description></item><item><title>50,000 feet</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-5/</guid><description>Purpose and principles Ultimate intention for something, and the standards for its success. Why are we doing this? What are the critical behaviors?
Principles describe more how you play the game than the game itself. They represent the ideal way to act and be in a particular arena (a project team, a company, a family) or in life in general.
Good to revisit periodically for quality control.
Examples I freely and spontaneously take the time to enjoy the simple and profound pleasures of life.</description></item><item><title>Shell boilerplate</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/shell-boilerplate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/shell-boilerplate/</guid><description>#!/bin/bash readonly program=&amp;#34;$(basename &amp;#34;${0}&amp;#34;)&amp;#34; usage() { cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;USAGE Description Usage: ${program} [&amp;lt;arguments&amp;gt;] ${program} -h | --help Options: -h --help Show this screen. USAGE } error() { printf &amp;#34;\terror: %s\n&amp;#34; &amp;#34;%@&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;amp;2 exit 1 } info() { printf &amp;#34;\tinfo: %s\n&amp;#34; &amp;#34;%@&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;amp;2 } command_1() { printf &amp;#34;${program}is unimplemented\n&amp;#34; } main() { if [[ ${1:-} =~ ^-h|--help$ ]]; then usage else command_1 &amp;#34;$@&amp;#34; fi } trap &amp;#39;error &amp;#34;errexit on line $LINENO with exit code: $?</description></item></channel></rss>