<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>aside on The views expressed</title><link>https://philoserf.com/topics/aside/</link><description>Recent content in aside on The views expressed</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://philoserf.com/topics/aside/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://philoserf.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/about/</guid><description>Colophon The views expressed is built by Hugo, hosted on GitHub Pages, and cached by Cloudflare. It is developed on an Apple MacBook using vscode, hyper, and zsh.
Content is written with a variety of editing tools. Text usually starts in Drafts on an iPhone or an iPad, and sometimes, even on an Apple watch. Some ideas gain flesh and substance with mind-mapping in MindNode. Content that takes time to develop is tracked with Things.</description></item><item><title>Papa doble</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/papa-doble/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/papa-doble/</guid><description>One of my favorite cocktails is the Papa Doble a.k.a the Hemingway Daquari, the Hemingway Special, and even the Hemingway Cocktail.
Various rifts on a theme The Educated Barfly How To Drink Steve the Bartender Behind the Bar Imbibe Magazine Distinguished Spirits Equal Parts Cocktail P. Allen Smith bestdrinkrecipes Bonus Let’s Talk Drinks</description></item><item><title>The social web</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/the-social-web/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/the-social-web/</guid><description>When it comes to the social web I have played with many alternatives over the years, including some paid offerings, because I did not want to be the product being sold. The problem with all of them, so far, is adoption. The people I want to follow are on Twitter, Facebook, Snapchat, Instagram, and LinkedIn. I no longer wish to be on those platforms. So I am not active on them.</description></item><item><title>Markdown syntax</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/markdown-syntax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/markdown-syntax/</guid><description>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.
Headings The following HTML &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt; is the highest section level while &amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; is the lowest.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo.</description></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/identity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/identity/</guid><description>You may call yourself by any name. Each identity has a shifting foundation.
What was liberal, isn&amp;rsquo;t. What was conservative, isn&amp;rsquo;t. Want was Democrat is now Republican and what was once Republican is now Democratic. What is at this moment will be different tomorrow while carrying the same name. Even our understanding of the meaning of a thing is infirm.
So grab the name you want today and use it. Wear it out.</description></item></channel></rss>