<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>list on The views expressed</title><link>https://philoserf.com/terms/list/</link><description>Recent content in list on The views expressed</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://philoserf.com/terms/list/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Podcasts</title><link>https://philoserf.com/podcasts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/podcasts/</guid><description>60-Second Science 99% Invisible All the Presidents' Lawyers Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick Another Way, by Lawrence Lessig Ardan Labs Podcast Arrested DevOps Audio Arguendo Automators AWS TechChat Backpacking Light Podcast Change Your Game with GTD Clearly Quaker Podcast Common Sense with Dan Carlin Consider This from NPR Dan Carlin&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History: Addendum Dan Carlin&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History Democracy in Danger Democracy Matters Democracy Paradox Democracy Works Editor&amp;rsquo;s Picks from The Economist Freakonomics Radio Fresh Air Future Hindsight Getting Things Done podcast from GTDnordic Getting Things Done Go Time Google Cloud Platform Podcast How Do We Fix It?</description></item><item><title>Backpacking Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/backpacking-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/backpacking-kit/</guid><description> coming soon</description></item><item><title>Computing Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/computing-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/computing-kit/</guid><description> Antigen Go programming language Hugo Hyper.js iPad iPhone MacBook Scapple Things vscode zsh</description></item><item><title>Driving Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/driving-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/driving-kit/</guid><description> Honda Element</description></item><item><title>Fitness Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/fitness-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/fitness-kit/</guid><description> Merrill Trail Gloves Strava Apple watch WaterRower</description></item><item><title>Writing Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/writing-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/writing-kit/</guid><description> Pilot Namiki fountain pen Pilot iroshizuku ama-iro ink</description></item><item><title>Now</title><link>https://philoserf.com/now/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/now/</guid><description>COVID-19 STATUS: Pfizer-BioNTech Vaccine Dose #2 I am …
aware of seasons in a renewed way given the return to a midwestern viewpoint going back to Seattle for a visit in late May … grateful for
my wife and our relationship the change in pace and focus brought on by pandemic isolation … dreaming of
the end of the pandemic and the life beyond … reading</description></item><item><title>Eating apples</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/eating-apples/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/eating-apples/</guid><description>Ambrosia Autumn Glory® Braeburn Breeze™ Cameo Cosmic Crisp® Crispin Daybreak Empire Envy™ Fuji Gala Gravenstein Hidden Rose Holstein Honeycrisp Jazz™ Jonagold JUICI™ Kanzi® Kiki™ KORU® Lady Alice® Liberty McIntosh Mutsu Opal® Pacific Rose™ Pazazz Pinata® Pink Lady® Rome Smitten™ Sonya™ Sugar Bee™ SweeTango® Sweetie™ Winesap more at Wikipedia</description></item><item><title>Article ideas</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/article_ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/article_ideas/</guid><description> a news bit with corporation person language removed on using tools vs play cask of amontillado with verbs redacted on coming to ruby via Chef, a journey on Gemfile, gemspec and patch-level dependency restrictions on play vs learning and 30 years of both on rubygems, gem generators, and 0.0.1 on rvm, rbenv, and chruby on the temperate rain forest on voraciously consuming information and contribution span of control on a rock face in Vermont, life lesson</description></item><item><title>Business writing</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/business-writing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/business-writing/</guid><description> Purpose: why the document is being written, the goals of the document Audience: who will read the document, include unintended audiences who might read your work Stakeholders: who may be affected by the document or project Context: the background of and situation in which the document is created State your thesis Write an outline Write the first draft Revise and polish</description></item><item><title>Canons of conduct</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/canons-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/canons-of-conduct/</guid><description>by Thomas Jefferson
never put off to tomorrow what you can do to-day. never trouble another with what you can do yourself never spend your money before you have it never buy a thing you do not want, because it is cheap, it will be dear to you. take care of your cents: Dollars will take care of themselves! pride costs us more than hunger, thirst and cold. we never repent of having eaten too little.</description></item><item><title>100 Thematic Writing Subjects</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/100-thematic-writing-subjects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/100-thematic-writing-subjects/</guid><description> Introduction Complicated Making History Rivalry Unbreakable Obsession Eternity Gateway Death Opportunities 33% Dead Wrong Running Away Judgment Seeking Solace Excuses Vengeance Love Tears My Inspiration Never Again Online Failure Rebirth Breaking Away Forever and a day Lost and Found Light Dark Faith Colors Exploration Seeing Red Shades of Grey Forgotten Dreamer Mist Burning Out of Time Knowing How Fork in the road Start Nature’s Fury At Peace Heart Song Reflection Perfection Everyday Magic Umbrella Party Troubling Thoughts Stirring of the Wind Future Health and Healing Separation Everything For You Slow Down Heartfelt Apology Challenged Exhaustion Accuracy Irregular Orbit Cold Embrace Frost A Moment in Time Dangerous Territory Boundaries Unsettling Revelations Shattered Bitter Silence The True You Pretense Patience Midnight Shadows Summer Haze Memories Change in the Weather Illogical Only Human A Place to Belong Advantage Breakfast Echoes Falling Picking up the Pieces Gunshot Possession Twilight Nowhere and Nothing Answers Innocence Simplicity Reality Acceptance Lesson Enthusiasm Game Friendship Endings</description></item><item><title>A list</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/a-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/a-list/</guid><description> Sleep Food Exercise Routine Early rise Drink water Attention upon intention Be, think, do Be, do, have Other people Purpose Own your life/moment Journal</description></item><item><title>A set of tests for writing</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/a-set-of-tests-for-writing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/a-set-of-tests-for-writing/</guid><description> the I believe ……. test the so what test the why test a single point overcome self doubt educate, entertain, or inspire action-outcome people need to belong to find meaning be passionate while you give it to your audience it not really about them, it is about what you care about do you have a driving need to share this story-driven premise-driven</description></item><item><title>Alphabet sentences</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/alphabet-sentences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/alphabet-sentences/</guid><description>A large fawn jumped quickly over white zinc boxes.
A mad boxer shot a quick, gloved jab to the jaw of his dizzy opponent.
A pox on you, jergens, old beanbag, you’ve squashed my favorite zwieback.
A quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog.
A quick movement of the enemy will jeopardize six gunboats.
About sixty codfish eggs will make a quarter pound of very fizzy jelly.
Alfredo just must bring very exciting news to the plaza quickly.</description></item><item><title>List of feelings</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/list-of-feelings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/list-of-feelings/</guid><description>Feelings when needs are satisfied Affectionate compassionate friendly loving open hearted sympathetic tender warm Engaged absorbed alert curious engrossed enchanted entranced fascinated interested intrigued involved spellbound stimulated Hopeful expectant encouraged optimistic Confidant empowered open proud safe secure Excited amazed animated ardent aroused astonished dazzled eager energetic enthusiastic giddy invigorated lively passionate surprised vibrant Grateful appreciative moved thankful touched Inspired amazed awed wonder Joyful amused delighted glad happy jubilant pleased tickled Exhilarated blissful ecstatic elated enthralled exuberant radiant rapturous thrilled Peaceful calm clear headed comfortable centered content equanimous fulfilled mellow quiet relaxed relieved satisfied serene still tranquil trusting Refreshed enlivened rejuvenated renewed rested restored revived Feelings when needs are not satisfied Afraid apprehensive dread foreboding frightened mistrustful panicked petrified scared suspicious terrified wary worried Annoyed aggravated dismayed disgruntled displeased exasperated frustrated impatient irritated irked Angry enraged furious incensed indignant irate livid outraged resentful Aversion animosity appalled contempt disgusted dislike hate horrified hostile repulsed Confused ambivalent baffled bewildered dazed hesitant lost mystified perplexed puzzled torn Disconnected alienated aloof apathetic bored cold detached distant distracted indifferent numb removed uninterested withdrawn Disquiet agitated alarmed discombobulated disconcerted disturbed perturbed rattled restless shocked startled surprised troubled turbulent turmoil uncomfortable uneasy unnerved unsettled upset Embarresesd ashamed chagrined flustered guilty mortified self-conscious Fatigue beat burnt out depleted exhausted lethargic listless sleepy tired weary worn out Pain agony anguished bereaved devastated grief heartbroken hurt lonely miserable regretful remorseful Sad depressed dejected despair despondent disappointed discouraged disheartened forlorn gloomy heavy hearted hopeless melancholy unhappy wretched Tense anxious cranky distressed distraught edgy fidgety frazzled irritable jittery nervous overwhelmed restless stressed out Vulnerability fragile guarded helpless insecure leery reserved sensitive shaky Yearning envious jealous longing nostalgic pining wistful</description></item><item><title>Needs</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/needs/</guid><description> Atmosphere: especially having the correct kind of lighting Presence or mindfulness (think switching off your phone!) Pleasure: treat smart food! Equality: we over me Gratitude: being thankful for what you have now Harmony: no place for competition or bragging Comfort: your surroundings Truce: no conflicts Togetherness Shelter: a feeling of safety</description></item><item><title>Traveller SFRPG Versions</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/traveller-sfrg-versions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/traveller-sfrg-versions/</guid><description> Traveller MegaTraveller Traveller: The New Era Marc Miller&amp;rsquo;s Traveller GURPS Traveller GURPS Traveller Interstellar Wars Traveller D20 Traveller Hero Mongoose Traveller 1ed Traveller 5ed Mongoose Traveller 2ed</description></item><item><title>Privately owned public spaces in Seattle</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/privately-owned-public-spaces-in-seattle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/privately-owned-public-spaces-in-seattle/</guid><description> 99 Union Street, Union St. plaza and stairs to Western Avenue 200 University Street, Hillclimb, atrium and transit tunnel access 600 Stewart Street, Arcade and setback 621 Union Street, Shopping arcade and plazas 700 5th Avenue, Plazas and retail space 701 5th Avenue, Atrium, shopping court and plazas 701 Pike Street, Shopping corridor and plazas 720 Olive Way, Wedge plaza 800 5th Avenue, Shopping arcade and plaza 900 University Street, Property setback 925 4th Avenue, Hillclimb, setback and atrium 999 3rd Avenue, Hillclimb and atrium 1000 2nd Avenue, Plaza 1001 4th Avenue, Plaza and retail space 1111 3rd Avenue, Arcade, plaza and retail space 1113 6th Avenue, Plaza and Arcade 1200 6th Avenue, Arcade and plaza 1201 3rd Avenue, Plaza 1300 1st Avenue, Hillclimb at University Street 1400 6th Avenue, Art, plaza and sidewalk improvements 1420 5th Avenue, Shopping corridor and atrium 1501 4th Avenue, Shopping corridor 1600 7th Avenue, Setback and plazas 2001 6th Avenue, Plaza 2033 6th Avenue, Plaza, arcade and setback 2201 9th Avenue, Green street, plaza and pedestrian improvements</description></item></channel></rss>