<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome on The views expressed</title><link>https://philoserf.com/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome on The views expressed</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://philoserf.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Podcasts</title><link>https://philoserf.com/podcasts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/podcasts/</guid><description>60-Second Science 99% Invisible All the Presidents' Lawyers Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick Another Way, by Lawrence Lessig Ardan Labs Podcast Arrested DevOps Art of Modern Ops Audio Arguendo Automators AWS TechChat Backpacking Light Podcast Change Your Game with GTD Changelog Clearly Quaker Podcast Common Sense with Dan Carlin Consider This from NPR Cycling Podcast Daily 202&amp;rsquo;s Big Idea Dan Carlin&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History: Addendum Dan Carlin&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History Democracy in Danger Democracy Matters Democracy Paradox Democracy Works Economist Asks Editor&amp;rsquo;s Picks from The Economist Field Guides Freakonomics Radio Fresh Air Future Hindsight Getting Things Done podcast from GTDnordic Getting Things Done Go Time Google Cloud Platform Podcast How Do We Fix It?</description></item><item><title>Now</title><link>https://philoserf.com/now/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/now/</guid><description>SARS CoV-2/COVID-19 status—fully vaccinated Pfizer-BioNTech I am …
back home in the midwest after a, too short, visit to the Seattle area … grateful for
my wife and our relationship … dreaming of
the many trips and gatherings ahead, including the Rockford gathering in July an, as yet, unplanned road trip in August my niece&amp;rsquo;s wedding in September an overnight, or long weekend, hiking trip in October a company gathering in early November another wedding in November a cruise in November and a, hopefully quiet, December … reading</description></item><item><title>Feature Template</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/feature-template/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/feature-template/</guid><description>Feature:NAME DESCRIPTION Background:NAME DESCRIPTION Given STEP_DESCRIPTION And STEP_DESCRIPTION Scenario Outline:NAME DESCRIPTION Given STEP_DESCRIPTION And STEP_DESCRIPTION &amp;#34;&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;&amp;#34; When STEP_DESCRIPTION But STEP_DESCRIPTION Then STEP_DESCRIPTION &amp;#34;&amp;lt;output&amp;gt;&amp;#34; And STEP_DESCRIPTION Example: |input|output||value|result||valve|result|</description></item><item><title>Food Rules</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/food-rules/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/food-rules/</guid><description>Eat Food Not too much Mostly plants source: Food Rules by Michael Pollan</description></item><item><title>Backpacking Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/backpacking-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/backpacking-kit/</guid><description> coming soon</description></item><item><title>Computing Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/computing-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/computing-kit/</guid><description> Antigen Go programming language Hugo Hyper.js iPad iPhone MacBook Scapple Things vscode zsh</description></item><item><title>Driving Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/driving-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/driving-kit/</guid><description> Honda Element</description></item><item><title>Fitness Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/fitness-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/fitness-kit/</guid><description> Merrill Trail Gloves Strava Apple watch WaterRower</description></item><item><title>Writing Kit</title><link>https://philoserf.com/writing-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/writing-kit/</guid><description> Pilot Namiki fountain pen Pilot iroshizuku ama-iro ink</description></item><item><title>Easier Goals</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/easier-goals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/easier-goals/</guid><description>Envision: Spend time each and every day envisioning your life as it will look after you have achieved your goal.
Assess: Create an honest assessment of where you stand at this moment in regards to your goal.
Strategize: Create a strategy that will get you from where you are to where you want to be.
Implement: Your strategy.
Evaluate: Your progress (or lack thereof) regularly. Tweak your assessment and strategy as necessary.</description></item><item><title>Kanban</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/kanban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/kanban/</guid><description>Fundamentals Visualize work Limit work-in-progress Method Start where you are Incremental, evolutionary change Respect the current process, roles, responsibilities, and titles Encourage acts of leadership at all levels Cards are nouns | Lanes are verbs Cards are things | Lanes are acivities What type of work is it? Where is it now? Where did it come from? Where will it go when I am done?</description></item><item><title>Places</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/places/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/places/</guid><description> Rockford, Michigan; less than one year Seattle, Washington (&amp;amp; environs); more than twenty years US Army; five years @ Fort Sill, Oklahoma; Fort Benning, Georgia; Çorlu (Tekirdağ, Türkiye Cumhuriyeti); &amp;amp; Fort Lewis, Washington Albany, New York; four years SUNY Albany &amp;amp; New York Army National Guard with the 10th Mountain Division US Army; four years @ Fort Benning, Georgia; Fort Lewis, Washington; &amp;amp; Vicenza (Veneto, Repubblica italiana) Dublin, Ohio (greater Columbus area); two years Lilburn, Georgia (greater Atlanta area); six years Jamestown, New York (far western southern tier); ten years</description></item><item><title>Eating apples</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/eating-apples/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/eating-apples/</guid><description>Ambrosia Autumn Glory® Braeburn Breeze™ Cameo Cosmic Crisp® Crispin Daybreak Empire Envy™ Fuji Gala Gravenstein Hidden Rose Holstein Honeycrisp Jazz™ Jonagold JUICI™ Kanzi® Kiki™ KORU® Lady Alice® Liberty McIntosh Mutsu Opal® Pacific Rose™ Pazazz Pinata® Pink Lady® Rome Smitten™ Sonya™ Sugar Bee™ SweeTango® Sweetie™ Winesap more at Wikipedia</description></item><item><title>ADHD note</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/adhd-note/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/adhd-note/</guid><description> emotional dis-regulation reaction sensitivity 3 Rs recognize respond reflect reframe green engage prepare yellow slow down calm down red disengage seek safety</description></item><item><title>André Gide Quote</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/andre-gide-quote/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/andre-gide-quote/</guid><description>Everything has been said already; but as no one listens, we must always begin again.
— André Gide</description></item><item><title>Article ideas</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/article_ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/article_ideas/</guid><description> a news bit with corporation person language removed on using tools vs play cask of amontillado with verbs redacted on coming to ruby via Chef, a journey on Gemfile, gemspec and patch-level dependency restrictions on play vs learning and 30 years of both on rubygems, gem generators, and 0.0.1 on rvm, rbenv, and chruby on the temperate rain forest on voraciously consuming information and contribution span of control on a rock face in Vermont, life lesson</description></item><item><title>Black Umbrellas</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/black-umbrellas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/black-umbrellas/</guid><description>On a rainy day in Seattle stumble into any coffee shop and look wounded by the rain. Say, Last time I was in I left my black umbrella here. A waitress in a blue beret will pull a black umbrella from behind the counter and surrender it to you like a sword at your knighting. Unlike New Englanders, she&amp;#39;ll never ask you to describe it, never ask what day you came in, she&amp;#39;s intimate with rain and its appointments.</description></item><item><title>Business writing</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/business-writing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/business-writing/</guid><description> Purpose: why the document is being written, the goals of the document Audience: who will read the document, include unintended audiences who might read your work Stakeholders: who may be affected by the document or project Context: the background of and situation in which the document is created State your thesis Write an outline Write the first draft Revise and polish</description></item><item><title>Canons of conduct</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/canons-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/canons-of-conduct/</guid><description>by Thomas Jefferson
never put off to tomorrow what you can do to-day. never trouble another with what you can do yourself never spend your money before you have it never buy a thing you do not want, because it is cheap, it will be dear to you. take care of your cents: Dollars will take care of themselves! pride costs us more than hunger, thirst and cold. we never repent of having eaten too little.</description></item><item><title>Chinese mountain poets</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/chinese-mountain-poets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/chinese-mountain-poets/</guid><description>by Li Bao You ask me why I dwell in the green mountain; I smile and make no reply for my heart is free of care. As the peach-blossom flows down stream and is gone into the unknown, I have a world apart that is not among men. by Du Mu After I climb the chill mountain&amp;#39;s steep stone paths, Deep in the white clouds there are homes of men. I stop my carriage, and sit to admire the maple-grove at nightfall, Whose frozen leaves are redder than the flowers of early Spring.</description></item><item><title>Collect, process, organize, review, and do</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/collect-process-orgainize-review-do/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/collect-process-orgainize-review-do/</guid><description>Collect what we might have action about or attention on. Process it – classify the commitment and decide the action step. Organize the results into action, reference, or on-hold, so we can Review the options to be comfortable and focused about what we Do at any point in time. Collect People have all kinds of ideas about a zillion things, and refile them somewhere in their mind. Additionally they are getting hundreds of communications a day, from emails to random interruptions.</description></item><item><title>Desired outcome</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-desired-outcome/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-desired-outcome/</guid><description>Any result you want to achieve or experience you want to have.
This is a broad catch-all category, which is designed to give you permission to capture anything that you might want (as little or big as that might be).
Examples Go for a hot-air balloon ride. Do a yoga hand-stand. Take a fabulous vacation trout fishing. Spend a day doing nothing. Meet the perfect tennis coach. Create a wonderful family reunion for Mom and Dad’s 50th Anniversary.</description></item><item><title>100 Thematic Writing Subjects</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/100-thematic-writing-subjects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/100-thematic-writing-subjects/</guid><description> Introduction Complicated Making History Rivalry Unbreakable Obsession Eternity Gateway Death Opportunities 33% Dead Wrong Running Away Judgment Seeking Solace Excuses Vengeance Love Tears My Inspiration Never Again Online Failure Rebirth Breaking Away Forever and a day Lost and Found Light Dark Faith Colors Exploration Seeing Red Shades of Grey Forgotten Dreamer Mist Burning Out of Time Knowing How Fork in the road Start Nature’s Fury At Peace Heart Song Reflection Perfection Everyday Magic Umbrella Party Troubling Thoughts Stirring of the Wind Future Health and Healing Separation Everything For You Slow Down Heartfelt Apology Challenged Exhaustion Accuracy Irregular Orbit Cold Embrace Frost A Moment in Time Dangerous Territory Boundaries Unsettling Revelations Shattered Bitter Silence The True You Pretense Patience Midnight Shadows Summer Haze Memories Change in the Weather Illogical Only Human A Place to Belong Advantage Breakfast Echoes Falling Picking up the Pieces Gunshot Possession Twilight Nowhere and Nothing Answers Innocence Simplicity Reality Acceptance Lesson Enthusiasm Game Friendship Endings</description></item><item><title>A list</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/a-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/a-list/</guid><description> Sleep Food Exercise Routine Early rise Drink water Attention upon intention Be, think, do Be, do, have Other people Purpose Own your life/moment Journal</description></item><item><title>A set of tests for writing</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/a-set-of-tests-for-writing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/a-set-of-tests-for-writing/</guid><description> the I believe ……. test the so what test the why test a single point overcome self doubt educate, entertain, or inspire action-outcome people need to belong to find meaning be passionate while you give it to your audience it not really about them, it is about what you care about do you have a driving need to share this story-driven premise-driven</description></item><item><title>Affirmation</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-affirmation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-affirmation/</guid><description>A written self-talk statement
Affirmations are statements about desired experiences or outcomes, written in the first-person present tense, with rich texture. Reading them should put you in the center of your own advertisements.
Examples I love the healthy way my body feels, toned and flexible, at its perfect weight. With positive cash flow and increasing financial reserves, I am experiencing an exhilarating sense of abundance and freedom. It is easy for me to express my affection for my family through my words and my touch.</description></item><item><title>Alphabet sentences</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/alphabet-sentences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/alphabet-sentences/</guid><description>A large fawn jumped quickly over white zinc boxes.
A mad boxer shot a quick, gloved jab to the jaw of his dizzy opponent.
A pox on you, jergens, old beanbag, you’ve squashed my favorite zwieback.
A quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog.
A quick movement of the enemy will jeopardize six gunboats.
About sixty codfish eggs will make a quarter pound of very fizzy jelly.
Alfredo just must bring very exciting news to the plaza quickly.</description></item><item><title>GTD task</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-task/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-task/</guid><description>Tasks are
observable activities that can be completed in one period of activity.</description></item><item><title>Ideal scene</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-ideal-scene/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-ideal-scene/</guid><description>A detailed description of a desired future. Ideal scenes can take on many forms – mocked-up articles in the press describing how extraordinarily successful your enterprise has been, collages with pictures and headlines that express what your life may look and feel like if you could have it like you want it, etc. It can simply be descriptive paragraphs written in an affirmational style. Wonderful to create and re-read and re-imagine on some regular basis.</description></item><item><title>Intention</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-intention/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-intention/</guid><description>A resolve toward a direction, value, outcome or purpose.
An intention can be used to express an inclination toward something – a desire for a more on-going way of being or acting as well as specific goals or results.
Examples I am consistently improving the range of my vocabulary. I am trusting my own judgment, insights, and decisions. The company is providing a rich environment for people to expand their personal and professional capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Intuition</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-intuition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-intuition/</guid><description>Hunches about where things are going and optimal approaches to it.
Intuitive insights are seldom recognized when we have them. It’s useful to notice when an awareness may be present in you and feed it back to yourself at a future time. It can sensitize and enhance your perceptive abilities.
Examples By the end of the year, I sense I will have met someone whom I consider masterful at my new hobby.</description></item><item><title>List of feelings</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/list-of-feelings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/list-of-feelings/</guid><description>Feelings when needs are satisfied Affectionate compassionate friendly loving open hearted sympathetic tender warm Engaged absorbed alert curious engrossed enchanted entranced fascinated interested intrigued involved spellbound stimulated Hopeful expectant encouraged optimistic Confidant empowered open proud safe secure Excited amazed animated ardent aroused astonished dazzled eager energetic enthusiastic giddy invigorated lively passionate surprised vibrant Grateful appreciative moved thankful touched Inspired amazed awed wonder Joyful amused delighted glad happy jubilant pleased tickled Exhilarated blissful ecstatic elated enthralled exuberant radiant rapturous thrilled Peaceful calm clear headed comfortable centered content equanimous fulfilled mellow quiet relaxed relieved satisfied serene still tranquil trusting Refreshed enlivened rejuvenated renewed rested restored revived Feelings when needs are not satisfied Afraid apprehensive dread foreboding frightened mistrustful panicked petrified scared suspicious terrified wary worried Annoyed aggravated dismayed disgruntled displeased exasperated frustrated impatient irritated irked Angry enraged furious incensed indignant irate livid outraged resentful Aversion animosity appalled contempt disgusted dislike hate horrified hostile repulsed Confused ambivalent baffled bewildered dazed hesitant lost mystified perplexed puzzled torn Disconnected alienated aloof apathetic bored cold detached distant distracted indifferent numb removed uninterested withdrawn Disquiet agitated alarmed discombobulated disconcerted disturbed perturbed rattled restless shocked startled surprised troubled turbulent turmoil uncomfortable uneasy unnerved unsettled upset Embarresesd ashamed chagrined flustered guilty mortified self-conscious Fatigue beat burnt out depleted exhausted lethargic listless sleepy tired weary worn out Pain agony anguished bereaved devastated grief heartbroken hurt lonely miserable regretful remorseful Sad depressed dejected despair despondent disappointed discouraged disheartened forlorn gloomy heavy hearted hopeless melancholy unhappy wretched Tense anxious cranky distressed distraught edgy fidgety frazzled irritable jittery nervous overwhelmed restless stressed out Vulnerability fragile guarded helpless insecure leery reserved sensitive shaky Yearning envious jealous longing nostalgic pining wistful</description></item><item><title>Needs</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/needs/</guid><description> Atmosphere: especially having the correct kind of lighting Presence or mindfulness (think switching off your phone!) Pleasure: treat smart food! Equality: we over me Gratitude: being thankful for what you have now Harmony: no place for competition or bragging Comfort: your surroundings Truce: no conflicts Togetherness Shelter: a feeling of safety</description></item><item><title>One Pager</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/one-pager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/one-pager/</guid><description>The Problem How do we communicate clearly in a business or technological setting?
The Solution Write a One Pager.
To write a good One Pager:
Write it in one page. Put a date at the top, so people know if it’s fresh or stale. Write a clear, short title. Write a single sentence problem description in the form of a question. Write the smallest solution description possible, while being complete and clear.</description></item><item><title>Traveller SFRPG Versions</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/traveller-sfrg-versions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/traveller-sfrg-versions/</guid><description> Traveller MegaTraveller Traveller: The New Era Marc Miller&amp;rsquo;s Traveller GURPS Traveller GURPS Traveller Interstellar Wars Traveller D20 Traveller Hero Mongoose Traveller 1ed Traveller 5ed Mongoose Traveller 2ed</description></item><item><title>GTD mastery checklist</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-mastery-checklist/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-mastery-checklist/</guid><description>The Basics I have read Getting Things Done from front to back. I have a calendar, which is always on hand. I use my calendar for appointments and day-specific items only. I have a physical inbox, which I use daily. I have an email program, set up the way I want it. I have voice mail, set up the way I want it. I always have a way to capture ideas and get them out of my head, in all contexts (notepad, laptop, voice recorder, etc.</description></item><item><title>20,000 feet</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-2/</guid><description>Areas of focus and responsibility Important spheres of work and life to be maintained at standards to “keep the engines running.”
This is a good checklist to review to ensure balance amidst all the roles you play and “hats” you wear. Review the whole list every so often, or pick one at a time and remind yourself at some interval: &amp;ldquo;How am I doing about XXXXX?&amp;rdquo;
Examples Work Staff development Planning Asset management Business development Quality control Personal Health/vitality Family Spiritual Career Recreation Household/administration Finances</description></item><item><title>30,000 feet</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-3/</guid><description>One- to two-year goals and objectives What do we want and need to accomplish, specifically, within the next 12 to 24 months, to make the vision happen?
Where is your job and personal life going? What will the role you’re in right now be looking like 12-24 months from now, based on your goals and on the directions of the changes at that level?
Examples Be debt free Company is 20% profitable Lose 10 pounds Sustain an exercise plan</description></item><item><title>40,000 feet</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-4/</guid><description>Three to five-year vision What it will look, sound, feel like with successful implementation. Long-term outcomes and ideal scenarios.
Visions represent larger outcomes that may take up to many years to create. Perhaps reviewed annually.
Examples Known as the leading innovator in our industry, internationally. Have written a best-selling novel. Shooting par golf. Being conversational in two more languages. Have established a not-for-profit foundation recognized for its contributions to the community.</description></item><item><title>50,000 feet</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/gtd-horizon-5/</guid><description>Purpose and principles Ultimate intention for something, and the standards for its success. Why are we doing this? What are the critical behaviors?
Principles describe more how you play the game than the game itself. They represent the ideal way to act and be in a particular arena (a project team, a company, a family) or in life in general.
Good to revisit periodically for quality control.
Examples I freely and spontaneously take the time to enjoy the simple and profound pleasures of life.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://philoserf.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/about/</guid><description>Colophon The views expressed is built by Hugo, hosted on GitHub Pages, and cached by Cloudflare. It is developed on an Apple MacBook using vscode, hyper, and zsh.
Content is written with a variety of editing tools. Text usually starts in Drafts on an iPhone or an iPad, and sometimes, even on an Apple watch. Some ideas gain flesh and substance with mind-mapping in MindNode. Content that takes time to develop is tracked with Things.</description></item><item><title>The rules</title><link>https://philoserf.com/the-rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/the-rules/</guid><description>Keep it simple. Make it when you need it.
If it has a name, do not give it another name. If you have given it a name, do not give it another name. Start with one file until you need another file. Start with one folder until you need another folder. Surrender or have a reason.
Adapt to the default configuration. After a sincere effort to adapt fails, change the default configuration.</description></item><item><title>Papa doble</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/papa-doble/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/papa-doble/</guid><description>One of my favorite cocktails is the Papa Doble a.k.a the Hemingway Daquari, the Hemingway Special, and even the Hemingway Cocktail.
Various rifts on a theme The Educated Barfly How To Drink Steve the Bartender Behind the Bar Imbibe Magazine Distinguished Spirits Equal Parts Cocktail P. Allen Smith bestdrinkrecipes Bonus Let’s Talk Drinks</description></item><item><title>Shell boilerplate</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/shell-boilerplate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/shell-boilerplate/</guid><description>#!/bin/bash readonly program=&amp;#34;$(basename &amp;#34;${0}&amp;#34;)&amp;#34; usage() { cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;USAGE Description Usage: ${program} [&amp;lt;arguments&amp;gt;] ${program} -h | --help Options: -h --help Show this screen. USAGE } error() { printf &amp;#34;\terror: %s\n&amp;#34; &amp;#34;%@&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;amp;2 exit 1 } info() { printf &amp;#34;\tinfo: %s\n&amp;#34; &amp;#34;%@&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;amp;2 } command_1() { printf &amp;#34;${program}is unimplemented\n&amp;#34; } main() { if [[ ${1:-} =~ ^-h|--help$ ]]; then usage else command_1 &amp;#34;$@&amp;#34; fi } trap &amp;#39;error &amp;#34;errexit on line $LINENO with exit code: $?</description></item><item><title>The social web</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/the-social-web/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/the-social-web/</guid><description>When it comes to the social web I have played with many alternatives over the years, including some paid offerings, because I did not want to be the product being sold. The problem with all of them, so far, is adoption. The people I want to follow are on Twitter, Facebook, Snapchat, Instagram, and LinkedIn. I no longer wish to be on those platforms. So I am not active on them.</description></item><item><title>Anattā</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/anatta/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/anatta/</guid><description>I may have groked what the Buddhist calls not-self, anattā.
I have had some part of my attention upon consciousness and time over the last few months. Not the surface definitions, not even the philosophical/physical conversation about the concepts. Instead, I have been attempting to grok the experience of consciousness and time.
That contemplation was my path to not-self. Compelling—if you happen to be &amp;ldquo;a set of causally interrelated psychophysical processes and events collocated in space and time&amp;rdquo; with my body and mind.</description></item><item><title>Markdown syntax</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/markdown-syntax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/markdown-syntax/</guid><description>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.
Headings The following HTML &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt; is the highest section level while &amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; is the lowest.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo.</description></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/identity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/identity/</guid><description>You may call yourself by any name. Each identity has a shifting foundation.
What was liberal, isn&amp;rsquo;t. What was conservative, isn&amp;rsquo;t. Want was Democrat is now Republican and what was once Republican is now Democratic. What is at this moment will be different tomorrow while carrying the same name. Even our understanding of the meaning of a thing is infirm.
So grab the name you want today and use it. Wear it out.</description></item><item><title>On the real terrain</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-real-terrain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-real-terrain/</guid><description>The clouds make a new terrain And the mind seeks to map this new terrain To the imagined real terrain below Then Clouds break And the mind maps The snow and the cloud Getting wrong the depth Mistaking one for the other And the other for the one All shifting imagination At these thirty five thousand feet</description></item><item><title>What we are about</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/what-we-are-about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/what-we-are-about/</guid><description>Chasing the sun westward At thirty five thousand feet, and On the remotest mountain valley Are the fingerprints of our fellow man The hard edges of our ordered way Between cloud and snow Define and declare who we are, and What we are about</description></item><item><title>Learning to code</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/learning-to-code/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/learning-to-code/</guid><description>Learning to program is like learning to read and write any foreign language. Lots of time will be spent looking at symbols that make little sense and hearing people speak about the language in terms that are, while familiar, carrying less meaning than perhaps they should. Lots of time will be spent reading references without context, then looking at language in context, then back and forth again.
Except, unlike spoken language, there are no translations to some language you already know.</description></item><item><title>Progymnasmata exercises</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/progymnasmata-exercises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/progymnasmata-exercises/</guid><description>A set of rudimentary exercises intended to prepare students of rhetoric for the creation and performance of complete practice orations (gymnasmata or declamations). A crucial component of classical and renaissance rhetorical pedagogy. Many progymnasmata exercises correlate directly with the parts of a classical oration.
Fable Narrative Chreia Proverb Refutation Confirmation Commonplace Encomium Vituperation Comparison Impersonation Description Thesis or Theme Defend / Attack a Law reference: Rhetoric at BYU</description></item><item><title>On the integration environment</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-integration-environment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-integration-environment/</guid><description>An integration environment is what a team provides to others so that others can integrate with the services provided by that team. The collection of all teams’ integration environments become, together, the notional “Integration Environment”.
A team’s integration environment may be constructed from the servers and services the team provides, and of the integration environments provided by other teams following the dependency model of each service. Ultimately, the full capabilities of our platform combine in the test agents that represent our external customers.</description></item><item><title>On Alerts</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/on-alerts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/on-alerts/</guid><description>source: from the Thoughtworks radar
In monitoring, the common approach is to conceive of erroneous conditions and set alerts when these appear. But it is often difficult to enumerate the myriad failure modes in a software system. Monitoring of invariants is a complementary approach to setting expected normal ranges, often by examining historical behavior, and alerting whenever a system goes outside those bounds.</description></item><item><title>Nordstrom Innovation Lab, empathy</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-empathy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-empathy/</guid><description> Open-ended Questioning Why? Tell me more? Deep Listening Back-to-Back Listening Emotional Response Profile Emotional Check-in</description></item><item><title>Nordstrom Innovation Lab, frameworks</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-frameworks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-frameworks/</guid><description> Business Model Canvas Lean Canvas Rainforest Canvas Jobs To Be Done Kaizen T User Stories Journey Mapping Personae ProtoPersona</description></item><item><title>Nordstrom Innovation Lab, methodologies</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-methodologies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-methodologies/</guid><description> Agile Lean Lean Startup Design Thinking Systematic Inventive Thinking Synectics Test Driven Development (TDD)</description></item><item><title>Nordstrom Innovation Lab, practices</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-practices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-practices/</guid><description> Kanban Make Work Visible Pairing Auditions Time Boxing Concierge MVP WIP 2x2 grid Triz Stop, start, more, less, Continue Flexible Work Spaces Kaizen</description></item><item><title>Nordstrom Innovation Lab, reading list</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-reading-list/</guid><description> Lean Startup Orbiting the Giant Hairball The Innovators Dilemma Innovators DNA GameStorming Small Bets The Toyota Way Gamestorming StrengthsFinder</description></item><item><title>Nordstrom Innovation Lab, rituals</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-rituals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/nordstrom-innovation-lab-rituals/</guid><description> Daily Standup (Big and Little) Weekly Retrospectives Show + Tell Lean Coffee</description></item><item><title>Perfect Health Diet supplement notes</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/perfect-health-diet-supplement-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/perfect-health-diet-supplement-notes/</guid><description>These “supplemental foods” we recommend eating on a regular schedule:
3 egg yolks daily, 5 yolks daily for women who are pregnant or planning to become pregnant (for choline, folate, vitamin A) A bowl of bone and joint broth soup, 3 days per week (for calcium, phosphorus, and collagen) Vegetables such as tomato, avocado, potato, sweet potato, banana, green leafy vegetables, and seaweeds such as dulse, daily (for potassium) Dark chocolate (&amp;gt;70%), as desired ¼ lb beef or lamb liver, weekly (copper, vitamin A, folate, choline) fish, shellfish, eggs, and kidneys, weekly (for selenium) OPTIONAL: 1 tablespoon red palm oil, weekly (vitamin E) These are supplements we recommend be taken daily:</description></item><item><title>Rubyist</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/rubyist/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/rubyist/</guid><description>include &amp;#39;everyone&amp;#39; ruby_community.each do |rubyist| give hug if rubyist.accept? :hugs awesome.lightning_talk (rubyist self).pairing do write.test case test.status when :red code.write when :green code.refactor end end until code.happy round_of.drinks end</description></item><item><title>Privately owned public spaces in Seattle</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/privately-owned-public-spaces-in-seattle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/privately-owned-public-spaces-in-seattle/</guid><description> 99 Union Street, Union St. plaza and stairs to Western Avenue 200 University Street, Hillclimb, atrium and transit tunnel access 600 Stewart Street, Arcade and setback 621 Union Street, Shopping arcade and plazas 700 5th Avenue, Plazas and retail space 701 5th Avenue, Atrium, shopping court and plazas 701 Pike Street, Shopping corridor and plazas 720 Olive Way, Wedge plaza 800 5th Avenue, Shopping arcade and plaza 900 University Street, Property setback 925 4th Avenue, Hillclimb, setback and atrium 999 3rd Avenue, Hillclimb and atrium 1000 2nd Avenue, Plaza 1001 4th Avenue, Plaza and retail space 1111 3rd Avenue, Arcade, plaza and retail space 1113 6th Avenue, Plaza and Arcade 1200 6th Avenue, Arcade and plaza 1201 3rd Avenue, Plaza 1300 1st Avenue, Hillclimb at University Street 1400 6th Avenue, Art, plaza and sidewalk improvements 1420 5th Avenue, Shopping corridor and atrium 1501 4th Avenue, Shopping corridor 1600 7th Avenue, Setback and plazas 2001 6th Avenue, Plaza 2033 6th Avenue, Plaza, arcade and setback 2201 9th Avenue, Green street, plaza and pedestrian improvements</description></item><item><title>zsh notes</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/zsh-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/zsh-notes/</guid><description>zsh startup and shutdown condition first second always /etc/zshenv ${HOME}/.zshenv login /etc/zprofile ${HOME}/.zprofile interactive /etc/zshrc ${HOME}/.zshrc login at startup /etc/zlogin ${HOME}/.zlogin login at shutdown ${HOME}/.zlogout /etc/zlogout use if [[ -o rcs ]]; then ... to prevent execution after first in zshenv
from man reading zcompile to pre-compile</description></item><item><title>Microtasks</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/microtasks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/microtasks/</guid><description>source: Steve Pavlina
Here’s an example 20-step microtask breakdown for the task of writing a new blog article. The steps are in sequential order:
Define a primary objective for the article (inform, persuade, entertain, or inspire). Brainstorm topic ideas, or review the list of reader-submitted topic suggestions. Select a topic. Do a quick and dirty, free-form writing session to get ideas down without regard to structure. Decide how to organize the ideas for clarity (chronological, topical, hierarchical, sequential, etc).</description></item><item><title>One Poetry #2</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 1986 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-2/</guid><description>Poetry that&amp;#39;s written To entertain oneself Has a value of its own Just like a little elf Who runs around And picks his toes And doesn&amp;#39;t have a care Who runs about Without clothes In the morning air.</description></item><item><title>One Poetry #1</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 1984 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-1/</guid><description>More poetry is written Than every will be read. Still, we apply pen to paper. Scratch and slide Words unfold Are found. Melody in voice, Expressed.</description></item></channel></rss>