<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>grand rapids on The views expressed</title><link>https://philoserf.com/terms/grand-rapids/</link><description>Recent content in grand rapids on The views expressed</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://philoserf.com/terms/grand-rapids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Places</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/places/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/places/</guid><description> Rockford, Michigan; less than one year Seattle, Washington (&amp;amp; environs); more than twenty years US Army; five years @ Fort Sill, Oklahoma; Fort Benning, Georgia; Çorlu (Tekirdağ, Türkiye Cumhuriyeti); &amp;amp; Fort Lewis, Washington Albany, New York; four years SUNY Albany &amp;amp; New York Army National Guard with the 10th Mountain Division US Army; four years @ Fort Benning, Georgia; Fort Lewis, Washington; &amp;amp; Vicenza (Veneto, Repubblica italiana) Dublin, Ohio (greater Columbus area); two years Lilburn, Georgia (greater Atlanta area); six years Jamestown, New York (far western southern tier); ten years</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://philoserf.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/about/</guid><description>Colophon The views expressed is built by Hugo, hosted on GitHub Pages, and cached by Cloudflare. It is developed on an Apple MacBook using vscode, hyper, and zsh.
Content is written with a variety of editing tools. Text usually starts in Drafts on an iPhone or an iPad, and sometimes, even on an Apple watch. Some ideas gain flesh and substance with mind-mapping in MindNode. Content that takes time to develop is tracked with Things.</description></item></channel></rss>