<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>poem on The views expressed</title><link>https://philoserf.com/terms/poem/</link><description>Recent content in poem on The views expressed</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://philoserf.com/terms/poem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Black Umbrellas</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/black-umbrellas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/black-umbrellas/</guid><description>On a rainy day in Seattle stumble into any coffee shop and look wounded by the rain. Say, Last time I was in I left my black umbrella here. A waitress in a blue beret will pull a black umbrella from behind the counter and surrender it to you like a sword at your knighting. Unlike New Englanders, she&amp;#39;ll never ask you to describe it, never ask what day you came in, she&amp;#39;s intimate with rain and its appointments.</description></item><item><title>Chinese mountain poets</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/chinese-mountain-poets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/chinese-mountain-poets/</guid><description>by Li Bao You ask me why I dwell in the green mountain; I smile and make no reply for my heart is free of care. As the peach-blossom flows down stream and is gone into the unknown, I have a world apart that is not among men. by Du Mu After I climb the chill mountain&amp;#39;s steep stone paths, Deep in the white clouds there are homes of men. I stop my carriage, and sit to admire the maple-grove at nightfall, Whose frozen leaves are redder than the flowers of early Spring.</description></item><item><title>On the real terrain</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-real-terrain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-real-terrain/</guid><description>The clouds make a new terrain And the mind seeks to map this new terrain To the imagined real terrain below Then Clouds break And the mind maps The snow and the cloud Getting wrong the depth Mistaking one for the other And the other for the one All shifting imagination At these thirty five thousand feet</description></item><item><title>What we are about</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/what-we-are-about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/what-we-are-about/</guid><description>Chasing the sun westward At thirty five thousand feet, and On the remotest mountain valley Are the fingerprints of our fellow man The hard edges of our ordered way Between cloud and snow Define and declare who we are, and What we are about</description></item><item><title>Rubyist</title><link>https://philoserf.com/notes/rubyist/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/notes/rubyist/</guid><description>include &amp;#39;everyone&amp;#39; ruby_community.each do |rubyist| give hug if rubyist.accept? :hugs awesome.lightning_talk (rubyist self).pairing do write.test case test.status when :red code.write when :green code.refactor end end until code.happy round_of.drinks end</description></item><item><title>One Poetry #2</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 1986 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-2/</guid><description>Poetry that&amp;#39;s written To entertain oneself Has a value of its own Just like a little elf Who runs around And picks his toes And doesn&amp;#39;t have a care Who runs about With out clothes In the morning air.</description></item><item><title>One Poetry #1</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 1984 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-1/</guid><description>More poetry is written Than every will be read. Still, we apply pen to paper. Scratch and slide Words unfold Are found. Melody in voice, Expressed.</description></item></channel></rss>