<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on The views expressed</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on The views expressed</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://philoserf.com/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Papa doble</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/papa-doble/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/papa-doble/</guid><description>One of my favorite cocktails is the Papa Doble a.k.a the Hemingway Daquari, the Hemingway Special, and even the Hemingway Cocktail.
Various rifts on a theme The Educated Barfly How To Drink Steve the Bartender Behind the Bar Imbibe Magazine Distinguished Spirits Equal Parts Cocktail P. Allen Smith bestdrinkrecipes Bonus Let’s Talk Drinks</description></item><item><title>Shell boilerplate</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/shell-boilerplate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/shell-boilerplate/</guid><description>#!/bin/bash readonly program=&amp;#34;$(basename &amp;#34;${0}&amp;#34;)&amp;#34; usage() { cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;USAGE Description Usage: ${program} [&amp;lt;arguments&amp;gt;] ${program} -h | --help Options: -h --help Show this screen. USAGE } error() { printf &amp;#34;\terror: %s\n&amp;#34; &amp;#34;%@&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;amp;2 exit 1 } info() { printf &amp;#34;\tinfo: %s\n&amp;#34; &amp;#34;%@&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;amp;2 } command_1() { printf &amp;#34;${program}is unimplemented\n&amp;#34; } main() { if [[ ${1:-} =~ ^-h|--help$ ]]; then usage else command_1 &amp;#34;$@&amp;#34; fi } trap &amp;#39;error &amp;#34;errexit on line $LINENO with exit code: $?</description></item><item><title>The social web</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/the-social-web/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/the-social-web/</guid><description>When it comes to the social web I have played with many alternatives over the years, including some paid offerings, because I did not want to be the product being sold. The problem with all of them, so far, is adoption. The people I want to follow are on Twitter, Facebook, Snapchat, Instagram, and LinkedIn. I no longer wish to be on those platforms. So I am not active on them.</description></item><item><title>Anattā</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/anatta/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/anatta/</guid><description>I may have groked what the Buddhist calls not-self, anattā.
I have had some part of my attention upon consciousness and time over the last few months. Not the surface definitions, not even the philosophical/physical conversation about the concepts. Instead, I have been attempting to grok the experience of consciousness and time.
That contemplation was my path to not-self. Compelling—if you happen to be &amp;ldquo;a set of causally interrelated psychophysical processes and events collocated in space and time&amp;rdquo; with my body and mind.</description></item><item><title>Markdown syntax</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/markdown-syntax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/markdown-syntax/</guid><description>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.
Headings The following HTML &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt; is the highest section level while &amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; is the lowest.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo.</description></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/identity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/identity/</guid><description>You may call yourself by any name. Each identity has a shifting foundation.
What was liberal, isn&amp;rsquo;t. What was conservative, isn&amp;rsquo;t. Want was Democrat is now Republican and what was once Republican is now Democratic. What is at this moment will be different tomorrow while carrying the same name. Even our understanding of the meaning of a thing is infirm.
So grab the name you want today and use it. Wear it out.</description></item><item><title>On the real terrain</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-real-terrain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-real-terrain/</guid><description>The clouds make a new terrain And the mind seeks to map this new terrain To the imagined real terrain below Then Clouds break And the mind maps The snow and the cloud Getting wrong the depth Mistaking one for the other And the other for the one All shifting imagination At these thirty five thousand feet</description></item><item><title>What we are about</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/what-we-are-about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/what-we-are-about/</guid><description>Chasing the sun westward At thirty five thousand feet, and On the remotest mountain valley Are the fingerprints of our fellow man The hard edges of our ordered way Between cloud and snow Define and declare who we are, and What we are about</description></item><item><title>Learning to code</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/learning-to-code/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/learning-to-code/</guid><description>Learning to program is like learning to read and write any foreign language. Lots of time will be spent looking at symbols that make little sense and hearing people speak about the language in terms that are, while familiar, carrying less meaning than perhaps they should. Lots of time will be spent reading references without context, then looking at language in context, then back and forth again.
Except, unlike spoken language, there are no translations to some language you already know.</description></item><item><title>On the integration environment</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-integration-environment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/on-the-integration-environment/</guid><description>An integration environment is what a team provides to others so that others can integrate with the services provided by that team. The collection of all teams’ integration environments become, together, the notional “Integration Environment”.
A team’s integration environment may be constructed from the servers and services the team provides, and of the integration environments provided by other teams following the dependency model of each service. Ultimately, the full capabilities of our platform combine in the test agents that represent our external customers.</description></item><item><title>One Poetry #2</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 1986 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-2/</guid><description>Poetry that&amp;#39;s written To entertain oneself Has a value of its own Just like a little elf Who runs around And picks his toes And doesn&amp;#39;t have a care Who runs about Without clothes In the morning air.</description></item><item><title>One Poetry #1</title><link>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 1984 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://philoserf.com/articles/one-poetry-1/</guid><description>More poetry is written Than every will be read. Still, we apply pen to paper. Scratch and slide Words unfold Are found. Melody in voice, Expressed.</description></item></channel></rss>